http://www.matsmatsmats.com/privacy.html

Learn: How Anti-Fatigue Mats Help
Learn: Rent or Buy?
Learn: Chemical Reactivity Guide
Learn: Chemicals and EPDM Rubber
Learn: What are UL, ETL, & NRTL?
Bars
Inclines (Wedges)
All Dance Products
Ballet Bars (Wall-Mount)
Ballet Bars (Portable)
Carpet Mat with Your Logo
Bamboo Chair Mat (Roll-Up)
Bamboo Chair Mat (Tri-Fold)
Learn: Yoga Disciplines
Learn: Yoga Poses (Asanas)
Maintenance & Installation
We Respect Your Privacy And Won't Share Your Personal Information
MatsMatsMats.com has developed this privacy policy as an extension of our commitment to combine the finest quality products
and services with the highest level of integrity in dealing with our customers. All personal information provided by customers
to MatsMatsMats.com will be held in strict confidence and will only be used for one of two purposes:
1. Your personal information such as shipping address, billing address and email address will only be provided to outside
shipping companies we use to ship your order, and outside credit card processing companies we use to bill you for the goods
and services you purchase. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any
secondary purposes.
2. Your personal information such as shipping address, billing address and email address will never be provided to any other
entities, and will be used only by MatsMatsMats.com for the purpose of communicating with you regarding your order or to
disseminate occasional product and website news to you. Most such communication will occur via email.
Security
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.
We will maintain appropriate safeguards to ensure that the security, integrity and privacy of your information is protected.
These measures include the collection of personal information only on pages which are secured by a secure TLS certificate and by proper network security.
Review and Correction
At any time you can review and correct any information you provided to us that was in error or has changed by
contacting us via our website or by calling 877-777-6287.
Third Party Intermediaries
We use an outside shipping company to ship orders, and a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services.
These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.
Questions and comments?
The MatsMatsMats.com Customer Privacy Policy has been developed out of respect for the privacy preferences and choices of
our customers and prospects. We have established procedures to ensure that every reasonable effort is made to address your
concerns. Any unresolved customer concerns can be addressed by
contacting us via our website or by calling 877-777-6287.
What else should I know about my privacy when online?
MatsMatsMats.com may contain some links to other Web sites. MatsMatsMats.com is not responsible for the privacy practices
or the content of such Web sites. MatsMatsMats.com does not share any of the individual personal information you provide
with the companies to which MatsMatsMats.com links.
Legal Disclaimer
Though we make every effort to preserve your privacy we may need to disclose personal information when required by law or
in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the edicts of the law or comply with a legal
process served on our Web site.
Your Consent To This Agreement
By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of your information by MatsMatsMats.com as specified above.
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what
information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.
Contacting the Web Site
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with our company, you
can contact us at:
MatsMatsMats.com
6303 Owensmouth Ave.
10th Floor
Woodland Hills, CA 91367
Phone & Fax: 877-777-6287
Send us a message
